Episode,Title,Date,Length,Entities,Entity_Types
1,David Krakauer on The Landscape of 21st Century Science,2019-10-09, 46:32 ,"(David Krakauer, The Landscape of 21st Century Science)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
2,"The Origins of Life: David Krakauer, Sarah Maurer, and Chris Kempes at InterPlanetary Festival 2019",2019-10-09, 55:37 ,"(The Origins of Life:, David Krakauer, Sarah Maurer, Chris Kempes, InterPlanetary Festival 2019)","['WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'EVENT']"
3,Sabine Hauert on Swarming Across Scales,2019-10-16, 39:23 ,"(Sabine Hauert, Swarming Across Scales)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
4,Luis Bettencourt on The Science of Cities,2019-10-23, 50:17 ,"(Luis Bettencourt, The Science of Cities)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
5,Jennifer Dunne on Food Webs & ArchaeoEcology,2019-10-30, 46:24 ,"(Jennifer Dunne, Food Webs & ArchaeoEcology)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
6,Jennifer Dunne on Reconstructing Ancient Food Webs,2019-11-06, 48:05 ,"(Jennifer Dunne,)",['PERSON']
7,"Rajiv Sethi on Stereotypes, Crime, and The Pursuit of Justice",2019-11-13, 59:39 ,"(Rajiv Sethi,)",['PERSON']
8,Olivia Judson on Major Energy Transitions in Evolutionary History,2019-11-20, 01:04:17 ,"(Olivia Judson, Major Energy Transitions in Evolutionary History)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
9,Mirta Galesic on Social Learning & Decision-making,2019-11-27, 01:19:23 ,"(Mirta Galesic, Social Learning & Decision)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
10,Melanie Moses on Metabolic Scaling in Biology & Computation,2019-12-04, 01:06:12 ,"(Melanie Moses, Biology & Computation)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
11,"Ray Monk on The Lives of Extraordinary Individuals: Wittgenstein, Russell, Oppenheimer",2019-12-11, 50:13 ,"(Ray Monk, The Lives of Extraordinary Individuals, Wittgenstein, Russell, Oppenheimer)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'ORG']"
12,Matthew Jackson on Social & Economic Networks,2019-12-18, 01:05:47 ,"(Matthew Jackson, Social & Economic Networks)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
13,W. Brian Arthur (Part 1) on The History of Complexity Economics,2020-01-08, 57:03 ,"(W. Brian Arthur, 1, The History of Complexity Economics)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
14,W. Brian Arthur (Part 2) on The Future of The Economy,2020-01-15, 01:00:49 ,"(W. Brian Arthur, 2, The Future of The Economy)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
15,R. Maria del-Rio Chanona on Modeling Labor Markets & Tech Unemployment,2020-01-22, 50:06 ,"(R. Maria del-Rio Chanona, Modeling Labor Markets & Tech)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
16,Andy Dobson on Disease Ecology & Conservation Strategy,2020-01-29, 59:12 ,"(Andy Dobson, Disease Ecology & Conservation Strategy)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
17,Chris Kempes on The Physical Constraints on Life & Evolution,2020-02-05, 01:02:22 ,"(Chris Kempes, The Physical Constraints on Life & Evolution)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
18,Kirell Benzi on Data Art & The Future of Science Communication,2020-02-12, 01:06:06 ,"(Kirell Benzi, Data Art & The Future of Science Communication)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
19,David B. Kinney on the Philosophy of Science,2020-02-19, 55:43 ,"(David B. Kinney, the Philosophy of Science)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
20,Albert Kao on Animal Sociality & Collective Computation,2020-02-26, 52:38 ,"(Albert Kao, Animal Sociality & Collective Computation)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
21,Melanie Mitchell on Artificial Intelligence: What We Still Don't Know,2020-03-04, 01:17:16 ,"(Melanie Mitchell, Artificial Intelligence)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
22,Nicole Creanza on Cultural Evolution in Humans & Songbirds,2020-03-11, 01:06:19 ,"(Nicole Creanza, Cultural Evolution in Humans & Songbirds)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
23,Andy Dobson on Epidemic Modeling for COVID-19,2020-03-18, 36:14 ,"(Andy Dobson, Epidemic Modeling)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
24,Laurent Hébert-Dufresne on Halting the Spread of COVID-19,2020-03-25, 49:14 ,"(Laurent Hébert-Dufresne,)",['PERSON']
25,Sam Scarpino on Modeling Disease Transmission & Interventions,2020-04-01, 28:32 ,"(Sam Scarpino, Modeling Disease Transmission & Interventions)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
26,Rigorous Uncertainty: Science During COVID-19 with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 1),2020-04-06, 47:04 ,"(David Krakauer, 1)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
27,COVID-19 & Complex Time in Biology & Economics with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 2),2020-04-13, 42:21 ,"(COVID-19 & Complex Time in, Biology & Economics, David Krakauer, 2)","['ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
28,Caroline Buckee on Improving COVID-19 Surveillance & Response,2020-04-16, 45:05 ,"(Caroline Buckee, Improving COVID-19 Surveillance & Response)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
29,"On Coronavirus, Crisis, and Creative Opportunity with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 3)",2020-04-20, 44:11 ,"(David Krakauer, 3)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
30,Rethinking Our Assumptions During the COVID-19 Crisis with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 4),2020-04-27, 51:13 ,"(David Krakauer, 4)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
31,Embracing Complexity for Systemic Interventions with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 5),2020-05-04, 44:55 ,"(David Krakauer, 5)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
32,"Exponentials, Economics, and Ecology with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 6)",2020-05-11, 47:28 ,"(David Krakauer, 6)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
33,The Future of the Human Climate Niche with Tim Kohler & Marten Scheffer,2020-06-02, 56:35 ,"(Tim Kohler & Marten Scheffer,)",['ORG']
34,Better Scientific Modeling for Ecological & Social Justice with David Krakauer (Transmission Series Ep. 7),2020-06-08, 40:03 ,"(Better Scientific Modeling for Ecological & Social Justice, David Krakauer, 7)","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
35,Scaling Laws & Social Networks in The Time of COVID-19 with Geoffrey West (Part 1),2020-06-17, 49:30 ,"(Geoffrey West, 1)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
36,"Geoffrey West on Scaling, Open-Ended Growth, and Accelerating Crisis/Innovation Cycles: Transcendence or Collapse? (Part 2)",2020-06-24, 58:18 ,"(Geoffrey West, 2)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
37,The Art & Science of Resilience in the Wake of Trauma with Laurence Gonzales,2020-07-06, 59:23 ,"(The Art & Science of Resilience, Laurence Gonzales)","['ORG', 'PERSON']"
38,"Fighting Hate Speech with AI & Social Science (with Joshua Garland, Mirta Galesic, and Keyan Ghazi-Zahedi)",2020-07-15, 01:05:48 ,"(AI & Social Science, Joshua Garland, Mirta Galesic, Keyan Ghazi-Zahedi)","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']"
39,Fractal Conflicts & Swing Voters with Eddie Lee,2020-07-23, 01:02:35 ,"(Eddie Lee,)",['PERSON']
40,The Information Theory of Biology & Origins of Life with Sara Imari Walker (Big Biology Podcast Crossover),2020-08-12, 01:06:51 ,"(Sara Imari Walker,)",['PERSON']
41,Natalie Grefenstette on Agnostic Biosignature Detection,2020-09-02, 56:52 ,"(Natalie Grefenstette,)",['PERSON']
42,Carl Bergstrom & Jevin West on Calling Bullshit: The Art of Skepticism in a Data-Driven World,2020-09-16, 58:44 ,"(Carl Bergstrom, The Art of Skepticism in a Data-Driven World)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
43,Vicky Yang & Henrik Olsson on Political Polling & Polarization: How We Make Decisions & Identities,2020-09-30, 01:10:09 ,"(Vicky Yang, Henrik Olsson, Political Polling & Polarization)","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG']"
44,"Introducing Alien Crash Site, a new SFI Podcast with host Caitlin McShea",2020-10-09, 20:32 ,"(Caitlin McShea,)",['PERSON']
45,David Wolpert on The No Free Lunch Theorems and Why They Undermine The Scientific Method,2020-10-14, 52:13 ,"(David Wolpert,)",['PERSON']
46,Helena Miton on Cultural Evolution in Music and Writing Systems,2020-10-29, 01:01:44 ,"(Helena Miton, Cultural Evolution in Music and Writing Systems)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
47,Scott Ortman on Archaeological Synthesis and Settlement Scaling Theory,2020-11-11, 54:54 ,"(Scott Ortman, Archaeological Synthesis and Settlement Scaling Theory)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
48,Peter Dodds on Text-Based Timeline Analysis & New Instruments for The Science of Stories,2020-11-26, 01:30:23 ,"(Peter Dodds, Timeline Analysis & New Instruments for)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
49,"Artemy Kolchinsky on ""Semantic Information"" & The Physics of Meaning",2020-12-11, 01:01:51 ,"(Artemy Kolchinsky, Semantic Information"" & The Physics of Meaning)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']"
50,Science in The Time of COVID: Michael Lachmann & Sam Scarpino on Lessons from The Pandemic,2020-12-23, 59:14 ,"(Michael Lachmann &, Sam Scarpino)","['ORG', 'PERSON']"
51,Cris Moore on Algorithmic Justice & The Physics of Inference,2021-01-14, 01:11:40 ,"(Cris Moore, Algorithmic Justice & The Physics of Inference)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
52,Mark Moffett on Canopy Biology & The Human Swarm,2021-01-28, 01:12:05 ,"(Mark Moffett, Canopy Biology & The Human)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
53,"Alien Crash Site Invades Complexity: Tamara van der Does on Sci-Fi Science, with Guest Co-host Caitlin McShea",2021-02-11, 50:08 ,"(Tamara van der, Sci-Fi Science, Caitlin McShea)","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON']"
54,David Stork on AI Art History,2021-02-25, 01:00:23 ,"(David Stork,)",['PERSON']
55,James Evans on Social Computing and Diversity by Design,2021-03-11, 01:00:11 ,"(James Evans, Social Computing and Diversity by Design)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
56,J. Doyne Farmer on The Complexity Economics Revolution,2021-03-26, 01:04:00 ,"(J. Doyne Farmer, The Complexity Economics Revolution)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
57,Jonas Dalege on The Physics of Attitudes & Beliefs,2021-04-08, 47:40 ,"(Jonas Dalege, The Physics of Attitudes & Beliefs)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
58,Orit Peleg on the Collective Behavior of Honeybees & Fireflies,2021-04-23, 01:00:58 ,"(Orit Peleg, the Collective Behavior of Honeybees & Fireflies)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
59,Sidney Redner on Statistics and Everyday Life,2021-05-07, 57:59 ,"(Sidney Redner, Statistics and Everyday Life)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
60,"Andrea Wulf on The Invention of Nature, Part 1: Humboldt's Naturegemälde",2021-05-20, 51:08 ,"(Andrea Wulf, The Invention of Nature, Part 1, Humboldt)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE']"
61,"Andrea Wulf on The Invention of Nature, Part 2: Humboldt's Dangerous Idea",2021-06-03, 48:54 ,"(Andrea Wulf, The Invention of Nature, Part 2, Humboldt)","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE']"
62,"Mark Ritchie on A New Thermodynamics of Biochemistry, Part 1",2021-06-17, 40:45 ,"(Mark Ritchie, 1)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
63,"Mark Ritchie on A New Thermodynamics of Biochemistry, Part 2",2021-07-01, 45:48 ,"(Mark Ritchie, 2)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
64,Reconstructing Ancient Superhighways with Stefani Crabtree and Devin White,2021-07-15, 01:06:01 ,"(Stefani Crabtree, Devin White)","['PERSON', 'PERSON']"
65,Deborah Gordon on Ant Colonies as Distributed Computers,2021-07-29, 54:15 ,"(Deborah Gordon, Ant Colonies as Distributed Computers)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
66,Katherine Collins on Better Investing Through Biomimicry,2021-08-14, 01:06:28 ,"(Katherine Collins, Better Investing Through Biomimicry)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
67,Tyler Marghetis on Breakdowns & Breakthroughs: Critical Transitions in Jazz & Mathematics,2021-09-08, 01:04:19 ,"(Tyler Marghetis, Breakdowns & Breakthroughs: Critical Transitions)","['PERSON', 'ORG']"
68,W. Brian Arthur on Economics in Nouns and Verbs (Part 1),2021-09-23, 51:56 ,"(W. Brian Arthur, 1)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
69,"W. Brian Arthur (Part 2) on ""Prim Dreams of Order vs. Messy Vitality"" in Economics, Math, and Physics",2021-10-06, 01:03:09 ,"(W. Brian Arthur, 2, Prim Dreams of Order, Physics)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG']"
70,Lauren Klein on Data Feminism (Part 1): Surfacing Invisible Labor,2021-10-22, 46:10 ,"(Lauren Klein, 1)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
71,Lauren Klein on Data Feminism (Part 2): Tracing Linguistic Innovation,2021-11-05, 33:23 ,"(Lauren Klein, 2)","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']"
72,Simon DeDeo on Good Explanations & Diseases of Epistemology,2021-11-24, 01:21:03 ,"(Simon DeDeo,)",['PERSON']
